ACTWU's Legal Department Records 5619/017
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Highland Yarn Mills, Inc. Case no.11-CA-15883, 1994 (Box 126, Folder 3)
- Highland Yarn Mills, Inc. Settlement, 1994 (Box 126, Folder 4)
- Highland Settlement Discussions/ Settlement Papers, 1994 (Box 126, Folder 5)
- Phil Cohen v. Florence + Jimmie Hill, 1994 (Box 126, Folder 6)
- Highland NLRB Papers, 1993-1995 (Box 126, Folder 7)
- Highland Yarn Mills, Inc. Case no.11-CA-14814, 1992 (Box 126, Folder 8)
  Pages 1-186. 6/15/1992
- Highland Yarn Mills, Inc. Case no.11-CA-14814, 1992 (Box 126, Folder 9)
  Pages 187-405. 6/16/1992
- Highland Yarn Mills, Inc. Case no.11-CA-14814, 1992 (Box 126, Folder 10)
  Pages 406-592. 6/17/1992
- Highland Yarn Mills, Inc. Case no.11-CA-14814, 1992 (Box 127, Folder 1)
  Pages 593-758. 6/18/1992
- Highland Yarn Mills, Inc. Case no.11-CA-14814, 1992 (Box 127, Folder 2)
  Pages 759-830. 6/19/1992
- Highland Yarn Mills, Inc. Case no.11-CA-14814, 1992 (Box 127, Folder 3)
  Pages 831-987. 6/22/1992
- Highland Yarn Mills, Inc. Case no.11-CA-14814, 1992 (Box 127, Folder 4)
  Pages 988-1218. 6/23/1992
- Highland Yarn Mills, Inc. Case no.11-CA-14814, 1992 (Box 127, Folder 5)
  Pages 1219-1462. 6/24/1992
- Highland Yarn Mills, Inc. Case no.11-CA-14814, 1992 (Box 127, Folder 6)
  Pages 1463-1542. 6/25/1992
- Highland Yarn Mills, Inc. Case no.11-CA-14814, 1992 (Box 127, Folder 7)
  Pages 1543-1647. 6/26/1992
- Highland Yarn Mills, Inc. Case no.11-CA-14814, 1992 (Box 127, Folder 8)
  Pages 1648-1704. 7/24/1992
- Reeves Brothers, Inc. Annette White Deposition, 1987 (Box 127, Folder 9)
  7/22/1987
- Reeves Brothers, Inc. Charles Lee Martin Deposition, 1987 (Box 127, Folder 10)
  7/21/1987
- Reeves Brothers, Inc. Michael Eugene Pryor Deposition, 1987 (Box 127, Folder 11)
- Reeves Brothers, Inc. Fred Crockett Wright Deposition, 1987 (Box 127, Folder 12)
  7/20/1987
- Reeves Brothers, Inc. Mac Byers Deposition, 1987 (Box 127, Folder 13)
- Reeves Brothers, Inc. v. ACTWU, 1987-1988 (Box 127, Folder 14)
- Reeves Brothers, Inc. Pension Plan, 1971-1984 (Box 127, Folder 15)
- Reeves Brothers, Inc. Pension Trust, 1971-1985 (Box 127, Folder 16)
- Reeves Brothers, Inc. Pension Plan, 1985-1987 (Box 127, Folder 17)
- Reeves Brothers, Inc. Pension Plan for Hourly Employees, 1978-1986 (Box 127, Folder 18)
- Reeves Brothers, Inc. Negotiations, 1987 (Box 127, Folder 19)
- Reeves Brothers, Inc. Supreme Court Reporter, 1973 (Box 127, Folder 20)
- Reeves Brothers, Inc. Raynor Deposition, 1987 (Box 127, Folder 21)
- Reeves Brothers, Inc. v. ACTWU Correspondence, 1987 (Box 127, Folder 22)
- Reeves Brothers, Inc. Settlement Agreement with Exhibits, 1987 (Box 127, Folder 23)
- Reeves Brothers (OSHA Material), 1986-1987 (Box 128, Folder 1)
- Reeves Brothers v. ACTWU Summaries of Interviews of Witnesses, 1987 (Box 128, Folder 2)
- Reeves Brothers, 1987 (Box 128, Folder 3)
- Reeves Brothers Union Distribution List Lawyers, 1987 (Box 128, Folder 4)
- Reeves Brothers Sign Contracts, 1987 (Box 128, Folder 5)
- Reeves Brothers Digest of Contents of Union Files, 1987 (Box 128, Folder 6)
- Reeves Brothers (Releases), 1987 (Box 128, Folder 7)
- Reeves Brothers, Inc. v. ACTWU et.al NCGS Section 75.1, 1987 (Box 128, Folder 8)
- Reeves Brothers et al. [folder 1 of 2], 1987 (Box 128, Folder 9)
- Reeves Brothers et al. [folder 2 of 2], 1987 (Box 128, Folder 10)
- Reeves Brothers, Inc. Matkowski Deposition, 1987 (Box 128, Folder 11)
- Reeves Brothers v. ACTWU Correspondence, 1987 (Box 128, Folder 12)
- Reeves Brothers, Inc. Bargaining, 1987 (Box 128, Folder 13)
- Reeves Brothers, Inc. v. ACTWU North Carolina, 1987-1990 (Box 128, Folder 14)
- Reeves Brothers, Inc. v. ACTWU Legal Research, 1987 (Box 128, Folder 15)
- Reeves Brothers Bargaining Notes, 1987 (Box 128, Folder 16)
- Reeves Brothers Shick Stock Certificates & Stock Powers, 1987 (Box 128, Folder 17)
- Schick, Inc. (Pension Suit), 1987 (Box 128, Folder 18)
- Schick v. ACTWU (Delaware), 1985-1987 (Box 128, Folder 19)
- ACTWU v. Schick (Reeves) 87-Civ 6043, 1987 (Box 128, Folder 20)
- ACTWU v. Schick (Delaware), 1987 (Box 128, Folder 21)
- Schick (Reeves) 10Q Report + Other Corporate Documents, 1987 (Box 129, Folder 1)
- Schick, Inc. Reeves Stockholders Suit, 1987 (Box 129, Folder 2)
- Reeves Brothers Pension Plan, 1987-1989 (Box 129, Folder 3)
- Reeves Brothers, Inc. Pension Material, 1982-1987 (Box 129, Folder 4)
- Reeves Notes + Misc., 1982-1987 (Box 129, Folder 5)
- Reeves Negotiations, 1987 (Box 129, Folder 6)
- Reeves Brothers, Inc. Arbitration Procedure, 1987 (Box 129, Folder 7)
- Reeves Brothers, Inc. v. ACTWU Police Reports & P.I. Reports, 1987 (Box 129, Folder 8)
- Reeves Contract, 1987-1989 (Box 129, Folder 9)
- Reeves Brothers, Inc. Notice of Arbitration, 1987-1988 (Box 129, Folder 10)
- Reeves Negotiations Company Information, 1981-1987 (Box 129, Folder 11)
- Reeves Draft of Rico Complaint, 1987 (Box 130, Folder 1)
- Reeves Brothers, Inc. NLRB Petition for Certiorari, 1988 (Box 130, Folder 2)
- Reeves Brothers, Inc. Alj Decision Cases no.11-CA-12195, 1989-1990 (Box 130, Folder 3)
- Reeves Brothers, Inc. 4th Circuit Enforcement, 1987-1988 (Box 130, Folder 4)
- Reeves Brothers, Inc. v. ACTWU Settlement Agreement by Schick, Inc., 1987 (Box 130, Folder 5)
- Reeves Brothers, Inc. Case no.11-CA-12299, 1987 (Box 130, Folder 6)
- Reeves Brothers Case no.11-RC-4592 and 277 NLRB153, 1986 (Box 130, Folder 7)
- Reeves Brothers, Inc. McCorkle, Kerley, Beatty, Lenster, 1981-1987 (Box 130, Folder 8)
- Reeves NLRB Case, 1986 (Box 130, Folder 9)
- Reeves Brothers, Inc. Case no.11-CA-12195, et al. NLRB Trial & Brief, 1987 (Box 130, Folder 10)
- Reeves Brothers, Inc. Case no.11-CA-12395 [folder 1 of 2], 1987 (Box 130, Folder 11)
- Reeves Brothers, Inc. Case #11-CA-12395 [folder 2 of 2], 1987 (Box 130, Folder 12)
- Reeves Brothers, Inc. Case no.11-CA-12313, 1987 (Box 130, Folder 13)
- Reeves Brothers, Inc. Case no.11-CA-12359, 1987 (Box 130, Folder 14)
- Reeves Brothers, Inc. Joe Rivens Discharge 11-CA-12369, 1986-1987 (Box 130, Folder 15)
- Reeves Brothers, Inc. Case no.11-CA-12254, 1985-1987 (Box 130, Folder 16)
- Reeves Brothers, Inc. Case no.11-CA-12133-1-2-3, 1986 (Box 130, Folder 17)
- Reeves Brothers, Inc. Case no.11-CA-12272, 1987 (Box 130, Folder 18)
- Reeves Brothers, Inc. Case no.11-CA-12231, 1986-1987 (Box 130, Folder 19)
- Reeves Brothers, Inc. Case no.11-CA-12298, 1987 (Box 130, Folder 20)
- Reeves Brothers, Inc. Case no.11-CA-12299, 1986-1987 (Box 130, Folder 21)
- Reeves Brothers, Inc. Case no.11-CA-12377, 1987 (Box 130, Folder 22)
- Reeves Brothers, Inc. Case no.11-CA-12282, 1987 (Box 131, Folder 1)
- Reeves Brothers, Inc. Case no.11-CB-1586, 1987 (Box 131, Folder 2)
- Tultex Legal Research, 1986-1990 (Box 131, Folder 3)
- Tultex Employer, 1987-1990 (Box 131, Folder 4)
- Tultex Union, 1981-1987 (Box 131, Folder 5)
- Tultex - Misc. Papers, 1990 (Box 131, Folder 6)
- Tultex 11-RC-5619 Research: Non-Legal, 1989-1990 (Box 131, Folder 7)
- Tultex Corporation no.11-RC-5619, 1989-1990 (Box 132, Folder 1)
- Tultex Transcripts, 1989 (Box 132, Folder 2)
- Tultex Transcripts, 1989 (Box 132, Folder 3)
- Reeves Brothers, Inc. Houston Deposition, 1987 (Box 133, Folder 1)
- Reeves Brothers, Inc. Drafts [folder 1 of 8], 1987 (Box 133, Folder 2)
- Reeves Brothers, Inc. Drafts [folder 2 of 8], 1987 (Box 133, Folder 3)
- Reeves Brothers, Inc. Drafts [folder 3 of 8], 1987 (Box 133, Folder 4)
- Reeves Brothers, Inc. Drafts [folder 4 of 8], 1987 (Box 133, Folder 5)
- Reeves Brothers, Inc. Drafts [folder 5 of 8], 1987 (Box 133, Folder 6)
- Reeves Brothers, Inc. Drafts [folder 6 of 8], 1987 (Box 133, Folder 7)
- Reeves Brothers, Inc. Drafts [folder 7 of 8], 1987 (Box 133, Folder 8)
- Reeves Brothers, Inc. Drafts [folder 8 of 8], 1987 (Box 133, Folder 9)
- Bates Nitewear Case no.11-CA-12090, 1985-1988 (Box 133, Folder 10)
- Bates Nitewear Union, 1985-1986 (Box 133, Folder 11)
- Bates Nitewear Company Case no.11-CA-12274, 1987 (Box 133, Folder 12)
- Bates/ESOP, 1987 (Box 133, Folder 13)
- Bates Nitewear Case no.11-CA-12129 Greensboro, N.C., 1986-1988 (Box 134, Folder 1)
- Bates Nitewear Company 11-RC-5345, 1986 (Box 134, Folder 2)
- Bates Nitewear Gerber Financial Filings, 1987-1988 (Box 134, Folder 3)
- Bates Nitewear Company Case no.11-CA-11785, 1986 (Box 134, Folder 4)
- Bates notes, 1987 (Box 134, Folder 5)
- Bates Nitewear Company Case no.11-RC-5345 Election Objections [folder 1 of 3], 1986-1988 (Box 134, Folder 6)
- Bates Nitewear Company Case no.11-RC-5345 Election Objections [folder 2 of 3], 1986-1987 (Box 134, Folder 7)
- Bates Nitewear Company Case no.11-RC-5345 Election Objections [folder 3 of 3], 1986 (Box 134, Folder 8)
- Bates Childrenswear, Inc. Case Nos. 11-CA-13086 + 13104, 1988-1989 (Box 134, Folder 9)
- Reeves Brothers, Inc. Deposition of Elijah Johnson [folder 1 of 2], 1987 (Box 134, Folder 10)
- Reeves Brothers, Inc. Deposition of Elijah Johnson [folder 2 of 2], 1987 (Box 134, Folder 11)
- Reeves Brothers, Inc. Deposition of Gary Dean Triplett, 1987 (Box 134, Folder 12)
- Reeves Brothers, Inc. Deposition of Theodore Joseph Green, 1987 (Box 134, Folder 13)
  8/25/1987
- Reeves Brothers, Inc. Deposition of Joel Arnold, 1987 (Box 134, Folder 14)
- Reeves Brothers, Inc. v. ACTWU Case no.11-CA-7824, 1987 (Box 134, Folder 15)
- Reeves Brothers, Inc. Statesville, NC, 1987 (Box 135, Folder 1)
  Pages 178-385 9/23/1987
- Reeves Brothers, Inc. Statesville, NC, 1987 (Box 135, Folder 2)
  Pages 484-676 10/14/1987
- Enro Shirt Company Arbitrations Willie Lacy EEOC Case, 1973-1979 (Box 135, Folder 3)
- EEOC v. Palm Beach Co. Extra Copies of Court Papers, 1984-1986 (Box 135, Folder 4)
- Palm Beach Company (Danville) Plant Closing EEOC, 1988 (Box 135, Folder 5)
- EEOC v. Palm Beach & ACTWU Exhibits to Dobbins Deposition, 1977-1979 (Box 135, Folder 6)
- EEOC v. Palm Beach Company & ACTWU Deposition of Stella Demaree, 1986 (Box 135, Folder 7)
- EEOC v. Palm Beach Company no.80-101 Correspondence [folder 1 of 2], 1982-1986 (Box 135, Folder 8)
- EEOC v. Palm Beach Company no.80-101 Correspondence [folder 2 of 2], 1974-1982 (Box 135, Folder 9)
- EEOC v. Palm Beach & ACTWU Depositions of Dowell, Williams, & Doyle, 1986 (Box 135, Folder 10)
- EEOC v. Palm Beach, et al Deposition of Garry Hughes, 1987 (Box 135, Folder 11)
- EEOC v. Palm Beach & ACTWU Depositions of James Giddings, 1987 (Box 135, Folder 12)
- EEOC v. Palm Beach Company et al. Deposition of Dr. Erich Prien, 1987 (Box 135, Folder 13)
- EEOC v. Palm Beach Company no.80-101 Correspondence, 1985-1987 (Box 135, Folder 14)
- EEOC v. Palm Beach Company no.80-101 Papers on Piecework and Time, etc., 1969-1985 (Box 136, Folder 1)
- EEOC v. Palm Beach Company & ACTWU KSA Labor Survey, 1974 (Box 136, Folder 2)
- Erlanger Warehouse Equal Pay Act Violations and Title VII Investigation, 1980 (Box 136, Folder 3)
- EEOC v. Palm Beach Company & ACTWU Depositions of Erich Prein and Jeffrey Schippman, 1987 (Box 136, Folder 4)
- EEOC v. Palm Beach Company #80-101 Civil Action Research and Constitution and Bylaws, 1974-1980 (Box 136, Folder 5)
- EEOC v. Palm Beach Company & ACTWU Depositions of Al Horn & Charles Pickard, 1987 (Box 136, Folder 6)
- EEOC v. Palm Beach Company, et al Deposition of Bobby Dobbins, 1987 (Box 136, Folder 7)
- EEOC v. Palm Beach Company & ACTWU Tapes of Plant Inspection, 1985-1987 (Box 136, Folder 8)
- EEOC v. Palm Beach Company & ACTWU Expert's Report, 1986 (Box 136, Folder 9)
- EEOC v Palm Beach Company, et al. Report of Co's Expert, 1987 (Box 136, Folder 10)
- EEOC v. Palm Beach Company no.80-101 Extra Copies of Court Papers, 1981-1982 (Box 136, Folder 11)
- EEOC v Palm Beach Company & ACTWU Attorney Work Product, 1987 (Box 136, Folder 12)
- EEOC Case (Carolyn L. Powell) & Local 365 Case no.110900663, 1989-1990 (Box 136, Folder 13)
- EEOC Palm Beach Company no.80-101, 1983-1984 (Box 136, Folder 14)
- EEOC v. Palm Beach Company Folder V, 1985-1986 (Box 136, Folder 15)
- EEOC v. Palm Beach Company Folver IV, 1984 (Box 136, Folder 16)
- EEOC v. Palm Beach Co. Folder IV, 1984 (Box 136, Folder 17)
- EEOC v. Palm Beach Co. Folder 11 [folder 1 of 2], 1982 (Box 136, Folder 18)
- EEOC v. Palm Beach Co. Folder 11 [folder 2 of 2], 1982 (Box 137, Folder 2)
- EEOC v. Palm Beach Company Litigation Folder 1 [folder 1 of 2], 1981 (Box 137, Folder 3)
- EEOC v. Palm Beach Company Litigation Folder 1 [folder 2 of 2], 1981 (Box 137, Folder 4)
- EEOC v. Palm Beach Company [folder 1 of 2], 1987 (Box 137, Folder 5)
- EEOC v. Palm Beach Company [folder 2 of 2], 1987 (Box 137, Folder 6)
- Farah Contracting, 1975-1976 (Box 137, Folder 7)
- Farah Manufacturing Company Farah Contract Negotiations, 1974 (Box 137, Folder 8)
- Farah Manufacturing Company Arbitration no.75-KO1881, 1974-1975 (Box 137, Folder 9)
- Farah Manufacturing Company (Temporary File) San Antonio, TX Arbitration, 1975 (Box 137, Folder 10)
- Farah Manufacturing Company Arbitrations, 1975-1976 (Box 137, Folder 11)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. Contract Administration, 1974 (Box 137, Folder 12)
- Farah Manufacturing Co, Inc. Profit Sharing Plan, 1984 (Box 137, Folder 13)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. San Antonio, Texas General [folder 1 of 2], 1975-1987 (Box 137, Folder 14)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. San Antonio, Texas General [folder 2 of 2], 1972-1974 (Box 137, Folder 15)
- Farah Manufacturing Company Form 10k, 1972-1973 (Box 137, Folder 16)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. Victoria, Texas, 1973-1975 (Box 137, Folder 17)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. General File, 1974-1976 (Box 137, Folder 18)
- Farah Meeting El Paso, 1975 (Box 137, Folder 19)
- Farah (Insurance Negotiations), 1976 (Box 137, Folder 20)
- Farah San Antonio No Distribution Rule, 1976 (Box 137, Folder 21)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. Polygraph Testing, 1975-1976 (Box 137, Folder 22)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. Denver, 1976 (Box 137, Folder 23)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. Colorado Plant, 1976 (Box 137, Folder 24)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. L-M Reports, 1973-1974 (Box 138, Folder 1)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. D-1s and D-2s, 1972-1973 (Box 138, Folder 2)
- Farah (Inspections), 1975 (Box 138, Folder 3)
- Farah Meeting, 1975 (Box 138, Folder 4)
  1-9-1975
- Farah Manufacturing Company Reports, 1975 (Box 138, Folder 5)
- Farah Manufacturing Company Arbitration El Paso, 1974-1976 (Box 138, Folder 6)
- Farah Manufacturing Co. Union Label Grievance, 1976 (Box 138, Folder 7)
- Farah Manufacturing Company Contracts and Agreements Collective Bargaining, 1975-1977 (Box 138, Folder 8)
- Farah Company Contract Between Farah & ACTWU, 1980 (Box 138, Folder 9)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. Settlements, 1974 (Box 138, Folder 10)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. Film, 1973-1974 (Box 138, Folder 11)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. Settlement, 1973 (Box 138, Folder 12)
- Farah Negotiations, 1976 (Box 138, Folder 13)
- Farah Negotiations Press Release, 1976 (Box 138, Folder 14)
- Farah Negotiations, 1977 (Box 138, Folder 15)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. Collective Bargaining Agreement and Settlement Papers, 1974 (Box 138, Folder 16)
- Farah General, 1983-1988 (Box 138, Folder 17)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, 1979-1980 (Box 138, Folder 18)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. Seniority Clause Issue El Paso, Texas, 1987 (Box 138, Folder 19)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. Salant Bid, 1989 (Box 138, Folder 20)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc., 1972-1974 (Box 139, Folder 1)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, 1979 (Box 139, Folder 2)
- Farah Contracting, 1975-1976 (Box 139, Folder 3)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, 1979 (Box 139, Folder 4)
- Farah Manufacturing Company Financing Statements, 1979 (Box 139, Folder 5)
- Farah Manufacturing Company Agreements, 1974 (Box 139, Folder 6)
- Farah Committee for the Development of Mass Communications, Inc., 1977 (Box 139, Folder 7)
- Farah Manufacturing Company Knitting and Weaving, 1975 (Box 139, Folder 8)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. Knitting and Weaving, 1975 (Box 139, Folder 9)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, Inc. Attorney Correspondence, 1973-1974 (Box 139, Folder 10)
- Farah Manufacturing Company Insurance Reopeners, 1976 (Box 139, Folder 11)
- Farah Manufacturing Company Knitting and Weaving, 1975-1976 (Box 139, Folder 12)
- Farah Manufacturing Company Bills of Particulars, 1974 (Box 139, Folder 13)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, 1973 (Box 139, Folder 14)
- Farah Manufacturing Company, 1976 (Box 139, Folder 15)
- Farah General, 1975-1978 (Box 139, Folder 16)
- Target Sportswear Proudfoot Grid System [folder 1 of 4], 1984 (Box 139, Folder 17)
- Target Sportswear Proudfoot Grid System [folder 2 of 4], 1981-1984 (Box 139, Folder 18)
- Target Sportswear Proudfoot Grid System [folder 3 of 4], 1982 (Box 139, Folder 19)
- Target Sportswear Proudfoot Grid System [folder 4 of 4], 1982 (Box 140, Folder 1)
- Farah Manufacturing Company Complaint Record [folder 1 of 2], 1982-1984 (Box 140, Folder 2)
- Farah Manufacturing Company Complaint Record [folder 2 of 2], 1983 (Box 140, Folder 3)
- Kootsouradis v. Brookevale Manufacturing Co., Inc. Index of Discovery Deposition Transcripts, 1984 (Box 140, Folder 4)
- ACTWU Local 887 Brookevale Manufacturing Arlene Mizwa 6-CB-6355, 1984 (Box 140, Folder 5)
- ACTWU Brookevale Mfg. Co. Marek Case no.6-CB-6404, 1984 (Box 140, Folder 6)
- Brookevale Manufacturing Inc. Case no.6-CA-16346, 1983-1984 (Box 140, Folder 7)
- Local 887 (Brookevale) Case no.6-CB-6343 Monessen, PA, 1984 (Box 140, Folder 8)
- Brookevale Manufacturing Co. Unemployment Ins. Appeal, 1983-1984 (Box 140, Folder 9)
- Brookevale Manufacturing Co. Discharge Arbitration Misc. Documents- Administratorship, 1982-1984 (Box 140, Folder 10)
- Target Sportswear Inc. Refusal to Furnish Info. On Grid, 1984 (Box 140, Folder 11)
- Brookevale Manufacturing Co. Discharge Arbitration, 1983-1984 (Box 140, Folder 12)
- Kootsouradis et. Al v. ACTWU Plaintiffs' answers to Interrogation, 1982-1984 (Box 140, Folder 13)
- Kootsouradis et. Al v. Brookevale Response to Plaintiff's Letter Requesting Documents, 1984 (Box 140, Folder 14)
- Kootsouradis et al. v. Brookevale Answer of Defendant Unions to Plaintiffs' Interrogatories and Response, 1983-1984 (Box 140, Folder 15)
- Kootsouradis et al v. ACTWU Civil Action no.84-1025 Depositions, 1983 (Box 141, Folder 1)
- Kootsouradis et al. v. ACTWU Deposition Transcripts, 1984 (Box 141, Folder 2)
- Henry Dropkin, 1984 (Box 141, Folder 3)
- Depositions v. Brookevale Manufacturing Co., Inc., 1984 (Box 141, Folder 4)
- Depositions v. Brookevale Manufacturing Co., Inc., 1984 (Box 141, Folder 5)
- Depositions v. Brookevale Manufacturing Co., Inc., 1984 (Box 141, Folder 6)
- Depositions v. Brookevale Manufacturing Co., Inc., 1984 (Box 141, Folder 7)
- Kootsouradis et al. v. Brookevale Manufacturing Co. and ACTWU Notes and Correspondence, 1984 (Box 141, Folder 8)
- Kootsouradis et al v. Brookevale Manufacturing Co. and ACTWU Notes and Correspondence, 1984 (Box 141, Folder 9)
- Kootsouradis et al v. Brookevale Mfg. Co. and ACTWU, 1984 (Box 142, Folder 1)
- Kootsouradis et al v. Brookevale Mfg. Co. and ACTWU, 1984 (Box 142, Folder 2)
- Standard Products Co. Rocky Mount, N.C., 1988 (Box 142, Folder 3)
- The Standard Products Co. 11-RC-5222, 1984-1989 (Box 142, Folder 4)
- Standard Products Company Rocky Mount, N.C., 1988 (Box 142, Folder 5)
- Standard Products (Affidavits), 1984 (Box 142, Folder 6)
- Standard Products Company, 1985-1989 (Box 142, Folder 7)
- Southeast Muffler Mfg. 11-CA-12438, 1987-1988 (Box 142, Folder 8)
- Standard Products Company Rocky Mount v. NLRB 4th Circuit Court of Appeals, 1986-1988 (Box 142, Folder 9)
- United Furniture Workers, 1985 (Box 142, Folder 10)
- Southeast Muffler Manufacturers. Case no.11-CA-12957, 1988 (Box 142, Folder 11)
- Southeast Muffler Mfg., Co. Case no.11-CA-12649, 1988-1989 (Box 142, Folder 12)
- Somersworth, Inc., 1984-1986 (Box 143, Folder 1)
- Cotton Garment Negotiations, 1982 (Box 143, Folder 2)
- Cotton Garment Negotiations, 1985-1986 (Box 143, Folder 3)
- Cotton Garment Negotiations Minutes, 1985 (Box 143, Folder 4)
- Cotton Garment Correspondence, 1985 (Box 143, Folder 5)
- Cotton Garment Correspondence Reopener Letters, 1985 (Box 143, Folder 6)
- Cotton Garment Ratification Votes, 1982 (Box 143, Folder 7)
- Cotton Garment Negotiation, 1982 (Box 143, Folder 8)
- Cotton Garment Supplement, 1985 (Box 143, Folder 9)
- Cotton Garment Agreements, 1986 (Box 143, Folder 10)
- Cotton Garment Negotiations, 1985 (Box 144, Folder 1)
- Sledge v. J.P. Stevens & Company, 1983 (Box 144, Folder 2)
  Sept.-Dec. 1983
- Sledge v. J.P. Stevens & Company Correspondence, 1983 (Box 144, Folder 3)
  August 1983
- Sledge v. J.P. Stevens & Company Decisions, Orders, Motions, 1980 (Box 144, Folder 4)
- J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Roanoke Rapids Contract Proofs, 1980 (Box 144, Folder 5)
- Sledge v. J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Decree and Decisions, 1975-1980 (Box 144, Folder 6)
- Sledge v. J.P. Stevens & Company Correspondence, 1985 (Box 144, Folder 7)
- Sledge v. J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc., 1986 (Box 144, Folder 8)
- Sledge v. J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc., 1990-1994 (Box 144, Folder 9)
- Sledge v. J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc., 1994-1995 (Box 145, Folder 1)
- Sledge v. J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. GK, 1995 (Box 145, Folder 2)
- Sledge v. J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Additional Volumes to Joint Appendix, 1995 (Box 145, Folder 3)
- Sledge v. J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Additional Volumes to Joint Appendix, 1972 (Box 146, Folder 1)
- Sledge v. J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Additional Volumes to Joint Appendix, 1990 (Box 146, Folder 2)
  Volume 6
- Sledge v. J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Brief for Defendant-Appellant, 1990 (Box 146, Folder 3)
- Sledge v. J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Brief for Defendant-Appellant, 1990 (Box 146, Folder 4)
- Sledge v. J.P. Stevens & Company, Inc. Joint Appendix, 1990 (Box 146, Folder 5)
- Catawba Valley Joint Board Merger Resolution, 1988 (Box 147, Folder 1)
  Merger of the Catawba Valley and Wester North Carolina Joint Boards and ballot returns.
- Termination of Catawba Valley Joint Board Administration, 1988 (Box 147, Folder 2)
  Resolution for removal of administration and the discharge of administrator duties. Ballot returns are included.
- Catawba Valley Joint Board Hearing on Administratorship, 1987 (Box 147, Folder 3)
  Testimonies, correspondence, and resolution drafts. Includes ballot returns.
- Catawba Valley Joint Board Administratorship, 1987-1988 (Box 147, Folder 4)
  Memorandums, resolutions, message copies, and miscellaneous documents.
- Hearing Officer's Report on South Jersey Joint Board, 1988 (Box 147, Folder 5)
  Report and distribution list.
- Termination and Merger of South Jersey Joint Board, 1987-1988 (Box 147, Folder 6)
  Resolutions and ballot returns for both the termination and the merger.
- Administratorship Status Reports Requests [Part 1 of 4], 1985-1986 (Box 147, Folder 7)
  Status reports and memorandums for January 13 to 16, 1986.
- Administratorship Status Reports Requests [Part 2 of 4], 1986 (Box 147, Folder 8)
  General Executive Board Meeting from March 17th to the 20th.
- Administratorship Status Reports Requests [Part 3 of 4], 1986 (Box 147, Folder 9)
  General Executive Board Meeting from July 14th to the 17th.
- Administratorship Status Reports Requests [Part 4 of 4], 1986 (Box 147, Folder 10)
  General Executive Board Meeting from October 28th to the 30th.
- Amalgamated Service and Allied Industry Joint Board, 1989 (Box 147, Folder 11)
  Resolution to establish administration and memorandum.
- Termination of South Jersey Joint Board Administratorship, 1988 (Box 147, Folder 12)
  Resolutions, correspondence, and status reports. General Executive Board Meeting from September 14th to the 16th.
- General Executive Board Meeting [Part 1 of 13], 1987 (Box 147, Folder 13)